{
    "id": "5a4393113766439d8e66055faa1eff01",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There are four stages …………….. the metamorphosis of a mosquito.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9b481db18b7f45e1a425070843253a7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t find anything ……………………. this messy desk.",
            "description": "On indicates position on the surface of something.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "74aa0016d2924ddd95013013b4efa572"
        },
        {
            "question": "Trying to define God led us ………………….. even more metaphysical questions.",
            "description": "Led is used with to.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd6c2471d1c4446da71299a635fc5a4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was praised ……………………… his meritorious service.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d2f0ef8e24b49eba5531889a1758d8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The caretaker showed no mercy ……………………. trespassers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02c3221bb59d4d8ca61923353df28581"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dickens was a great writer ……………………….. his tearful plots.",
            "description": "Although is a conjunction despite is used alone without of.",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "despite of",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5b39f888a300432a956323bfd2e7a68b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The car was going ………………………. its maximum speed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f581f809ef674330a1ee139da17d7eeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. the two examples, I prefer the latter.",
            "description": "Of is the correct word here.",
            "answers": [
                "From",
                "Of",
                "In"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4509e7261c18435aa96982c27507ecca"
        },
        {
            "question": "The clown made the children laugh ………………………… joy.",
            "description": "With is used in a number of expressions which say how people are showing their emotions. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c66075777dc84e318c93c88834a0faa1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The comedian finally got a laugh ………………………… the unresponsive audience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "593fe907629d4a6e8fb7badab96c4b4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will be a laughingstock …………………….. that silly outfit.",
            "description": "We use in to say what people are wearing. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5dc60ef2f92e40e993bae6631638ca2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I had her knack ……………………… cooking.",
            "description": "Knack is used with for.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d06146a2fd874385bcc580519cc5765b"
        }
    ]
}